<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Duncan Bradley</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Duncan Bradley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How an MRes Psychology programme has helped prepare me for my PhD</title>
      <link>/blog/blogpost1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blogpost1/</guid>
      <description>In September, I will start my PhD here at the University of Manchester, which will explore how people represent and interpret data visualisations. Over the last year, the MRes Psychology programme has given me opportunities to practice a variety of new skills and has provided me with a good foundation for my future studies.
The ‘Advanced Data Skills, Open Science and Reproducibility’ and ‘Advanced Statistics Workshop’ modules taught me about the assumptions behind statistical modelling techniques, and also provided useful maxims for navigating the complex world of analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>